时间到
Time!
好的  克林贡迷们  放下铅笔
All right, Klingons, pencils down.
好的  我这有 "pokh"[星际迷航里的克林贡语]
Okay, I have "pokh."
有了  有了
Have it. Got it.
"Potl"
"Potl."
有了  有了
Yup. Have it. Have it.
"Pukhpa"
"Pukhpa."
有了  有了
Have it. Got it. Yup.
我有"chorrr"
I have "chorrr."
有了
Got it. Yup.
-"Nekhmakh" -有了
-"Nekhmakh." -Yeah. Yeah.
和"kreplach"
And "kreplach."
等等  "Kreplach"吗
Hold on a second. "Kreplach?"
对
Yeah.
那不是克林贡语  那是依地语  意思是肉馅饺子
That isn't Klingon; it's Yiddish for meat-filled dumpling.
看来它也是克林贡语中的词语
Well, as it turns out, it's also a Klingon word.
真的吗  给它下个定义
Really? Define it.
"Kreplach":  美味的克林贡饺子
"Kreplach": A hearty Klingon... dumpling.
裁判怎么裁决
Judge's ruling?
不予采纳
Bilurrrbe.
大伙  我要看一下你们的电视
Hey, guys, I need to use your TV.
你的怎么了
What's wrong with your TV?
我也不知道  刚刚没影了
I don't know. It just died.
里面全是雪花
I'm getting a bunch of static.
你付你的有线电视费了吗
Did you pay your cable bill?
你这口气跟有线电视公司一样
Ugh, you sound just like the cable company.
好吧  大家安静
All right, so, shh!
泰拉·班克斯(超模之母)马上要从 全美超模大赛 里踢人了
Tyra Banks is about to kick someone off  America's Next Top Model.
抱歉  佩妮  但我们要
Excuse me, Penny, but we're...
别  别  别告诉她
No, no, don't tell her.
正在玩克林贡语拼字游戏
playing Klingon Boggle.
哦
Aw...
你"哦"什么
What do you mean, "Aw"?
难道她不知道我们是书呆子吗
Like she didn't know we were nerds?
好吧  如果你一定要看的话
All right, if you must watch,
那就请你静音  只看字幕
then mute it with closed captions, please.
随你
Fine.
好了  拼字斗士们  开始吧
All right, Boggle warriors... kapla'!
看看这些姑娘
Look at those women.
真是光彩照人啊
They're gorgeous.
"Worf"  不错  名词  当专有名词就太可惜了
Oh! "Worf," nice! Too bad that's a proper noun.
看那位  她就是未来的沃罗威茨夫人
Oh, look, the's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
不对  等等  那位才是
No, wait, that's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
头上戴着
With her head in the lap of...
真是太巧了  她才是未来的沃罗威茨夫人
Oh, what a coincidence. It's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
对  她们都可以搬去同你和你妈妈一起住
Yeah, and they can all move in with you and your mother.
现任的沃罗威茨夫人
The current Mrs. Wolowitz.
"qochbe'"是用嘴发音  还是用喉咙发音
Is "qochbe'" spelled with a  or a ?
为什么沃罗威茨夫人在哭呢
Why is that Mrs. Wolowitz crying?
那是阿娜伊斯
That's Anais.
房子里其她女孩都不喜欢她
None of the other girls in the house like her.
房子  什么房子
House? What house?
她们都居住在同一所房子里
They all live in a house together.
房子在哪
A house, where?
我不知道  洛杉矶的某个地方吧
I don't know. Somewhere in L.A.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你是说我只需开车就能到
You're telling me that I'm within driving distance
这些胸怀大志的超模们的住所吗
of a house filled with aspiring supermodels?
对  我想是的
Yeah, I guess.
她们住在一起  一同沐浴  还
And they live together and shower together and...
裸体枕头大战
have naked pillow fights?
你要去哪
Hey, wh-where are you going?
去付我的有线电视费
To pay my cable bill.
好的  放下铅笔
All right, pencils down!
我这有"lokh" "makh"和"cherrrkh"
I have "lokh," "makh," and "cherrrkh."
你们有吗
Anybody got those?
我错过什么了吗  她们把吉塞尔踢出去了吗
Did I miss anything? Did they kick Giselle off?
还没  不过她在水下拍的照片  真是丢死人了
Not yet, but her underwater photo shoot was an embarrassment.
很不幸  吉塞尔·沃罗威茨夫人对氯过敏
Sadly, Mrs. Giselle Wolowitz is sensitive to chlorine.
对她来说是好事  我喜欢出水芙蓉的大眼模特
Lucky for her I like my fashion models pruny and bug-eyed.
谢尔顿  食物买来了
Sheldon, the food's here.
到屋子了
Ooh, there's the house.
定格  快定格
Freeze frame, freeze frame.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
标记星辰位置和地理特征
Marking the star positions and physical landmarks
那样我们就能找到超模的屋子啦
so we can find the house of the supermodels.
为什么
Why?
这不是明摆着吗
Isn't it obvious?
她们每周都会踢出一个漂亮的女孩
Every week, they kick out a beautiful girl,
让她自尊受损  感觉在这里不受欢迎
making her feel unwanted and without self-esteem.
也可以叫未来的霍华德·沃罗威茨夫人
A.k.a. the future Mrs. Howard Wolowitz.
-我的中号汉堡好了吗  -好了
-Is my hamburger medium well? -Yes.
-片状莳萝  不甜的吗  -对
-Dill slices, not sweet? -Yes.
-调味品是单独包装吗  -对
-Individual relish packets? -Yes.
-有洋葱圈吗  -有
-Onion rings? -Yes.
-还有额外的面包吗  -我问了
-Extra breading? -I asked.
-他们怎么说  -没有  -你抗议了吗
-What did they say? -No. -Did you protest?
-是的  -吵架了吗  -没
-Yes. -Vociferously? -No.
那你怎么现在才来
Well, then what took you so long?
你就吃吧
Just eat.
大伙  我错过什么了吗
Hey, guys, what'd I miss? What'd I miss?
吉塞尔现在命悬一线
Giselle's hanging by a thread.
太好了  我讨厌她
Oh, good, I hate her.
那我们大喜之日就不邀请你了
Then you're not invited to our wedding.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
咱们还要看
Oh, do we have to suffer through this
这个暗箱操作严重的伪真人秀节目吗
transparently manipulative pseudo-reality again?
对
Yes.
咱俩有固定的电视节目表
You and I have a standing TV schedule,
那是我们多次争论和妥协的结果
which is the result of extensive debate and compromise.
除非是插播新闻  否则任何变更
Any alterations except for breaking news
都要在一周室友大会上提前获得批准
have to be pre-approved at the weekly roommate meeting.
写在议程里吧
Put it on the agenda.
但你必须先提案  才能写到议程里
But you have to make a motion to put it on agenda.
我可以提案呀  但你不会喜欢的
Oh, I'll make a motion, but you're not going to like it.
好吧  你就嘲笑议会程序吧
Fine. Mock Parliamentary procedure.
至少能把声音关掉吧
At least put it on mute.
吉赛尔根本不会被踢掉
Oh, Giselle's not getting kicked off.
穿得是越来越清凉了啊
It's totally going to be Summer.
咋啦
What?
谢尔顿的洋葱圈  快放回去
Sheldon's onion ring. Just put it back!
不过是个洋葱圈嘛
It's one onion ring.
在他发现前赶快放回去
Just put it back before he comes!
错错错
No, no, no!
我觉得原来不是放在那的
No, I don't think that's where it was.
他来了  大家不要承认啊
Okay, here he comes.  Deny, deny, people.
都别吭气
Wall of silence.
谁动了我的
Who touched my...
佩妮  佩妮干的
Penny! Penny did it.
你为什么要这么对我
Why would you do that?
不知道  我饿了
I don't know. I was hungry?
有什么大不了的
What's the big deal?
没有人可以动我盘子里的食物
The big deal is that nobody touches food on my plate.
好吧  我不知道  对不起了
All right. Look, I didn't know, I'm sorry.
我也对不起了  但你二振了
Well, I'm sorry, but that is your second strike.
什么
What?
你有两振了
You have two strikes.
三振出局
Three strikes and you're out.
这是个体育方面的暗喻
It's a sports metaphor.
体育方面的暗喻
A sports metaphor?
是的  棒球
Yes, baseball.
好吧  我加入
All right, yeah. I-I'll play along.
我什么时候一振的
What was my first strike?
三月十八号
March 18th.
你违反了我设立的禁止转发搞笑邮件的规定
You violated my rule about forwarding email humor.
我有吗
I did?
那只想吃"芝士汉包"的猫的图片
The photo of the cat who wants to "has cheezeburger"?
拜托  每个人都喜欢搞笑猫
Oh, come on. Everybody loves "LOL cats."
多可爱啊  它们是猫嘛所以不会拼写
They're cute and they can't spell 'cause they're cats.
我信任你才给你我的邮箱
I trusted you with my email address,
你发网络老古董给我  这就背叛了我对你的信任
and you betrayed that trust by sending me Internet banality:
一振
strike one.
动了我的食物  二振
Touching my food: strike two.
别担心  只在你的档案里保存一年
Don't worry. They only stay on your record for a year.
你也能早点把它们从你的档案里去掉  可就得去上他的课
You can get them removed early, but you have to take his class.
拜托  我就碰了一个洋葱圈
Come on, I touched one onion ring.
没错  但你又把它放回来了
Yeah, and then you put it back,
从而污染了其它洋葱圈
compromising the integrity of all the other onion rings.
亲爱的  你以后还想不想搭我的车了
Oh, honey, the buses don't go where you live, do they?
听着佩妮  我也想对你宽容一些
Look, Penny, I wish I could be more lenient with you,
但你现在已经是我们这个小团体的永久成员了
but since you've become a permanent member of our social group,
我就得告诉你一些大家都遵循的规矩
I have to hold you to the same standards as everybody else.
恭喜了  你正式成为我们中的一员
Congratulations. You're officially one of us.
新成员  新成员
One of us, one of us.
太激动了
Well, what a thrill.
你坐在我的位子上了
You're sitting in my spot.
天呐  别跟我开玩笑了
Oh, jeez, you've got to be kidding me.
莱纳德  她坐在我的位置上呢
Leonard, she's in my spot.
事情是这样的
Yeah, yeah. Uh, see, here's the thing.
你走了以后  我还要和他住在一起
After you leave, I still have to live with him.
我不管  我就坐这了
I don't care. I'm taking a stand.
这是个暗喻[taking a stand  明确立场]
Metaphorically.
那好吧  三振出局
All right, that's it. Strike three.
噢  三振
Ooh, strike three.
我被驱逐了
I'm banished?
什么东西啊
What the hell kind of crap is that?
别担心  我会和他谈谈的
Listen, don't worry. I'll talk to him.
没错  你谈吧
Yeah, you do that.
弱弱地问一句  你愿意来听他的课么
Just so I know, would you be open to taking his class?
你可以在网上听
You can do it online!
根据我们的三角测量法
So based on our triangulation,
我们锁定了超模的所在地
we've narrowed down the location of the Top Model house
在好莱坞山周围三平方英里内
to three square miles in the Hollywood Hills.
或者在北卡罗来纳的杜伦
Or possibly Durham, Noh Carolina.
我们找到的时候你想和我们一起去么
When we find it, you want to go with us?
去做什么
To do what?
和漂亮姑娘开派对啊
Party with the pretty girls, dude!
你疯了么
Are you insane?
你可去不成
You're not going to party with them.
你连接近那个地方都做不到
You're not even going to get anywhere near that place.
关于月球  当年他们也是对阿姆斯特朗[登月第一人]也是这么说的
That's what they said to Neil Armstrong about the moon.
没人对阿姆斯特朗说过这样的话
No one said anything of the kind to Neil Armstrong.
为了送一个人上月球
The entire nation dedicated a decade of effort and treasure
整个国家做出了十年的努力
to put a man on the moon.
我亲爱的美国兄弟们  不出今年
Well, my fellow Americans, before this year is out,
我们就可以把沃罗威茨送到一个超级模特身边去
we will put a Wolowitz on one of America's top models.
之后会有很多人认为这事从来没发生过
And a large number of people will believe it never happened.
让我想想
Okay, let me guess.
莱纳德要为乳糖不耐受人准备的配豆腐乳的油炸玉米粉饼
A quesadilla with soy cheese for the lactose-intolerant Leonard.
谢谢
Thank you.
不要杏仁的大虾凯撒沙拉
Shrimp Caesar salad with no almonds
是给极易过敏只在重大节日进行犹太洁食的霍华德的
for the highly allergic kosher-only-on-the-high-holidays Howard.
给我们突然回到印度饮食习惯的拉杰的是
And for our suddenly "back on the Hindu wagon" Raj,
专给爱吃肉的人准备的披萨不放肉
the meatlover's pizza, no meat.
马上就来
Coming right up.
等下
Wait. Excuse me.
你忘了我的烧烤培根芝士汉堡
You forgot my barbecue bacon cheeseburger,
烤肉酱  培根  芝士单放
barbecue sauce, bacon and cheese on the side.
我没告诉你么
Oh, I didn't tell you?
你被芝士蛋糕工厂驱逐了
You're banished from the Cheesecake Factory.
为什么
Why?
因为你三振了呀
Well, you have three strikes.
进门一振  坐下二振
One: coming in. Two: sitting down.
三振是因为我不喜欢你的态度
And three: I don't like your attitude.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
这不仅违反了加州法律
Not only is it a violation of California state law,
而且明目张胆地违背了芝士蛋糕工厂的规定
it flies directly in the face of Cheesecake Factory policy.
不会  现在有新的规定了
Yeah, no, there's a new policy:
日本人与谢尔顿不准进入
No shoes, no shirt, no Sheldon.
我打赌这种牌子一定能在帕萨迪纳大卖
I bet we could sell that sign all over Pasadena.
佩妮  我能和你说句话么
Penny, can I talk to you for a minute?
事情是这样的
Well, here's the thing.
我和谢尔顿谈过了 他也觉得自己过分
Um, I talked to Sheldon and he feels terrible
他也认为他有点不可理喻  有点过火了
and he agrees that he was unreasonable and out of line.
真的吗  那太好了
Really? Well, that's great.
是的  跟他道个歉  好吗
Yeah, so just apologize to him, okay?
什么  我干嘛要向那个疯子道歉
What? I'm not going to apologize to that nutcase.
别这样  其实很简单
Oh, come on. It's easy.
他还会亲自指导你怎么道歉
He'll even tell you what to say.
莱纳德  你还没开窍吗
Leard, don't you get it?
如果你们一味让他这样神经兮兮
If you guys keep going along with his insanity,
会助长他的气焰
you're just encouraging him.
才没有 我们是  卑躬屈膝
We're not encouraging. It's more like... knuckling under.
我喜欢和你们一起
Look, I like hanging out with you guys,
但我绝不会为莫须有的罪名道歉
but I'm not going to apologize for something I didn't do.
事实上  严格来说  你真的有做
Well, actually, technically, you did do it.
那是一振  莱纳德
That's strike one, Leonard.
这是你的油炸玉米粉饼
There you go: quesadilla.
沙拉
Salad.
还有你的披萨
There's your pizza.
在谢尔顿和本餐厅经理经过
And thanks to Sheldon's heated discussion
热烈讨论后
with my manager
一份烧烤汁加上熏肉奶酪分开放的
one barbecue bacon cheeseburger,
烤肉芝士汉堡送上
barbecue sauce, bacon and cheese on the side.
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气  尽情吃
Go ahead. Eat it.
有种就吃
I dare you
就是这里  找到了 我找到了全美超模
That's it. There's the house. I foundAmerica's top models!
真的吗
Are you sure?
看啊  房顶上
Look, on the roof.
阿娜伊斯和吉赛尔在晒日光浴
Anais and Giselle are sunbathing.
还是欧式的
European-style.
单从google的卫星地图  你就能把她们认出吗
You can recognize people on Google Earth?
当然不是
Of course not.
一个在北美防空联合司令部的哥们派了架间谍机去监视
I got a buddy of mine at NORAD to have a spy drone fly over.
北美防空联合司令部  你还动用了军用飞机
NORAD? You're using military aircraft?
它被设定任务 去西伯利亚核反应堆周边巡逻
It was already targeted to poke around a nuclear reactor in Siberia.
我也最多借来用一个小时
I took it an hour out of its way, tops.
好了  他在哪
Okay, where is he?
谢尔顿吗  我载他去了漫画店  怎么了
Sheldon? I just dropped him off at the comic book store. Why?
这  试试上网
Here. Try and go online.
-无线上网有问题吗  -你试试啊
Problem with the WiFi? Just try.
你好  乱抓汉堡的人
Greetings, hamburger toucher.
或许你在讶异
You are probably wondering
为什么你不能上网和朋友去聊一下
why you cannot IM with your little friends
你的生活是多么如此这般美妙
about how much you "heart" various things.
这段录像是在警告你
This recorded message is alerting you
你偷用我们的无线上网账号的日子
that I am putting an end
已经一去不复返
to your parasitic piggybacking upon our WiFi.
如果你想补救现状
If you want to remedy the situation,
你就自个儿打电话给电讯公司
you can contact the phone company,
自己开个无线账号  自己付钱  或者你可以跟我道歉
set up your own WiFi and pay for it, or you may apologize to me.
看
Well?
早说了  卑躬屈膝
I reiterate: knuckle under.
不不不  我要宣战了
No, no, no, no, no. It is on.
我要给你那位朋友点颜色瞧瞧
I am gonna introduce your friend to a world of hurt.
佩妮  没人想要跟谢尔顿 对着干
Oh, Penny, you don't want to get into it with Sheldon.
这人是从超级恶人实验室 事故里逃出来的
The guy is one lab accident away from being a supervillain.
我不管  我以前还是牛仔呢
I don't care. I was in junior rodeo.
不用一分钟  我就可以把他五花大绑还阉了
I can hogtie and castrate him in 60 seconds.
别这样对一个书呆子嘛
No need to neuter the nerd.
我能帮你上网
I can get you back online.
看  问题解决了
There, see? Problem solved.
好啦[依地语  犹太人使用的国际语]
Voil?
你好啊  小虫子
SHELDON: Hello, puny insects.
作为和我对着干的惩罚
As a consequence of your efforts to circumvent my will,
你们每人都额外增加一振
everyone is awarded one additional strike.
多亏你啊  霍华德
Thanks a lot, Howard.
你在哪里啰嗦什么
What are you complaining about?
我还要去接受他的教育
I'm the one who has to take the class again.
你好
Hello.
要去洗衣服吗
Time to do your laundry, huh?
周六晚嘛
It's Saturday night.
周六是洗衣之夜
Saturday is laundry night.
我知道
I know.
每个周六的8点15分
Every Saturday at 8:15.
老少咸宜
Easy to anticipate.
你这是什么意思
What are you implying?
我在说你是一个有生活习惯的人
I'm implying that you're a creature of habit.
如果因为某些事  周六晚上8点15分
And if something were to prevent you from doing your laundry
不能洗衣服
on Saturday at 8:15,
你会觉得
you might find it...
不爽
unpleasant.
甘拜下风吧
Knuckle under? My ass.
不是吧  所有的机器都有人用
Oh, no, are all the machines taken?
你该怎么办呢
What are you gonna do?
没问题
No problem.
换一个晚上再洗好了
I'll just do my laundry another night.
换一个晚上
Another night?
好吧  尽管试试
Well, I guess you can try,
但你内心深处
but deep inside your heart,
你知道洗衣之夜永远是周六晚上
you'll know that laundry night is always Saturday night.
女人  你在和一个智慧比你高的多的人较劲
Woman, you are playing with forces beyond your ken.
让你那高人一等的智慧见鬼去吧
Yeah, well, your ken can kiss my Barbie.
谢尔顿  谢尔顿
Sheldon. Sheldon!
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
怎么啦
Yes?
我的衣服都去哪儿了
Where are my clothes?
-你的衣服  -对  我把它们放在滚筒里洗
Your clothes? Yes, I left them in the washers
后来我再下去拿的时候它们就不见了
and when I went down to get them, they were gone.
真的吗
Really?
你没见那块牌子上写"不要远离在洗的衣物"么
Despite the sign that says "Do not leave laundry unattended"?
谢尔顿  我的衣服在哪儿
Sheldon, where are my clothes?
好像我是记得看到过一些女式内衣什么的
You know, I do recall seeing some female undergarments.
在哪儿呢
Where was that?
哦对
Oh, yes...
就是没多久之前
Earlier this evening,
我碰巧在眺望窗外的景色
I happened to gaze out the window
居然看到了一副罩罩
and a brassiere caught my eye.
你看看那个是不是呢
Do those look familiar?
你他娘的怎么把我衣服弄到电话线上去了
How the hell did you get them up on that telephone wire?
当你领悟到物理学的真谛之后  佩妮
When you understand the laws of physics, Penny,
一切皆有可能
anything is possible.
我能不能再加一句  木哈哈
And may I add: mwuh-ha-ha.
拿回来
Get them down.
-道歉  -绝不
Apologize. Never.
那你就去准备一根长棍子
Well, then may I suggest you get a very long stick
然后开始玩"挑裤衩"吧
and play panty pinata.
等等  谢尔顿  我们做得过头了
Look, wait, Sheldon, this has gotten out of hand, okay?
我干了一些蠢事
I've done some stupid things.
你也干了一些蠢事
You've done some stupid things.
我们就算扯平  大家平安度日  怎么样啊
How about we just call it even and move on with our lives?
我才没做蠢事
I've done no stupid things.
我已经作出让步了  你也应该有所表示
Look, you've got to meet me halfway here.
我有表示的
I am meeting you halfway.
我非常愿意承认  你做了一些蠢事
I'm willing to concede that you've done stupid things.
你们又开始说话了啊  太好了
Hey, you guys are talking again. Good.
又咋了
What happened?
莱纳德  记得我说我跟他较上了吗
Leonard, remember when I said it was on?
现在看来我要跟他没完了
Well, now it's junior rodeo on.
不是吧
Oh, not junior rodeo.
你干啥了
What did you do?
是她逼我的  莱纳德
I had no choice, Leonard.
她毁了我的洗衣之夜
She ruined laundry night.
木哈哈
Mwuh-ha-ha.
电话线不会把我电死的  对吧
Telephone wires can't electrocute you, can they?
不会  你是不是该收手了
No. Look, this has to stop.
不不不  这才刚开始呢
Oh, no, no, no. It is just beginning.
好吧  我实在是不想这么干  不过
All right, I really didn't want to do this, but...
给
here.
这是什么
What's this?
谢尔顿的致命弱点[超人剧集里的物质]
Sheldon's Kryptonite.
我的天
Oh, my God.
绝对不能告诉他是我给你的
He can never know that I gave that to you.
我是说过要给他点颜色瞧瞧
Look, I said I wanted to hurt him, but...
但这也太
but this?
用这个办法能大大缩短你们的战争耗时
It'll shorten the war by five years
从而拯救千百万人民
and save millions of lives.
停下  对了  就是这里
Oh, pause it. That's it. Confirmed.
我们找到超模们的地址了
We now have the address of the Top Model house.
上帝保佑你  谷歌街景注册商标
God bless you, Google Street View registered trademark.
你们两个
Okay, for the record,
这么做也太恶心了吧
what you're doing is really creepy.
告诉你  如果使用互联网
You know what? If it's "creepy"
还有军用卫星和机器飞艇
to use the Internet, military satellites, and robot aircraft
来定位一幢装满了火辣模特的房子
to find a house full of gorgeous young models
好让我不时去访问一下她们能叫"恶心"的话
so that I can drop in on them unexpectedly,
就好吧  就算我"恶心"好了
then fine, I'm "creepy."
喂
Hello.
你好  好的  稍等一下  我去叫他
Oh, hi. Yeah, hold on a second. I'll get him.
谢尔顿  你的电话
Sheldon, it's for you.
-谁打来的  -你妈妈
Who is it? Your mother.
好的
Oh, good.
妈妈  你好吗
Hi, Mom. How are you?
但  妈妈
But, Mom...
她老是坐我的专座
she keeps sitting in my spot.
还碰我的食物
And-and she touched my food.
是的  我是拿了她衣服  不过是她先挑拨我的
Okay, yes, I took her clothes, but she started it...
这太不公平了
No, that's not fair.
为什么我要去道歉
Why should I have to apologize?
我认为这点小事
Yeah, I really don't think this is the kind of thing
耶稣是不会来关心的
Jesus concerns himself with.
好吧我错了
No, you're right.
我不可能知道耶稣在想什么
I don't really know what Jesus thinks about.
好吧  再见
All right, good-bye.
是你告发我的吗
Did you tell on me?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我已经被两振了
I already have two strikes.
佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny.
佩妮
Penny.
我非常非常抱歉  我错了
I am very, very sorry for what I have done.
这是你的衣服
Here's your laundry.
我把你被振的次数清零了
I rescind your strikes
同样还取消对你的驱逐令
and you are no longer banished.
我能随便坐哪儿吗
Can I sit wherever I want?
算了  算了
Never mind, never mind.
那个不重要
That's, that's not important.
谢尔顿  你的气量很大
Sheldon, this was big of you.
谢谢  我非常感谢你
Thank you. I really appreciate it.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚安  谢尔顿
Good night, Sheldon.
佩妮
Penny...
怎么
Yes?
你够狠
Well played.
谢谢
Thank you.
记住  能力越大  责任越大[蜘蛛侠经典台词]
Just remember: with great power comes great responsibility.
了解了
Understood.
请问有事吗
Can I help you
有  我们是来修有线电视的
Yes, we here to fix the cable.
我们这里不是卫星电视吗
I think we have satellite.
我就是说卫星电视
That's what I meant.
好吧  请进
Oh. Okay, come on in.
她比我全家女人加起来都高
She's taller than all the women in my family combined.
现在我们干嘛
What do we do now?
跟着沃罗威茨夫人走
Follow Mrs. Wolowitz.